<html lang='en'>
<head>
<meta charset="UTF-8"/>
<title>Artist Statement</title>


<style>

.float-img {
float: left; 
margin-right: 10px; 
margin-bottom:5px; 
border: solid blue 1px; 
padding: 2px
}

</style>


</head>
<body>
<h1>
My Passion in Art
</h1>


<img src="https://1.bp.blogspot.com/-K-9GuvHFW0U/YVRrcoZ1FPI/AAAAAAAAQ2o/rXHP1ktNm3EyRO8FLlivjszZdqOqWfW4wCLcBGAsYHQ/w320-h234/art%2Bstatement.jpg
" width="280" height="280" alt="about me" title="aligning image and text." 
class="float-img"/>
  
  

 <h4><strong>Why I Paint:</strong></h4>
<p>My passion in art grew from the weekly art classes in primary school even though we would mostly just copy sample images drawn on a blackboard by the Art Teacher.
 </p> 

<p>Discovering artworks of world’s greatest artists were true sources of inspiration insofar as I would examine their masterpieces meticulously and try to replicate their techniques into my own artwork.
</p> 


<h4><strong>How I Paint:</strong></h4>

<p>The painting process starts with basic drawing of subject with help of online <a href="http://www.griddrawingtool.com">Grid Drawing Tool.</a> I use this grid drawing tool to retain proportionate dimensions of reference images while enlarging them on canvas.</p> 
  
<p>I first block the major shapes, designs and forms of subject in acrylic while laying the layout of artwork after which I then paint in oil.</p> 


<h4><strong>What I Paint:</strong></h4>
              
<p>I paint landscapes, portraits, wildlife and anything else that catches my eye. Every new painting is a learning experience for me. I feel I have been blessed with a special gift and it is incredibly satisfying to know that I can spread some inspirations and joy around through my artworks.</p> 

    
<p>The medium of my artworks is primarily in oil although I use acrylic for blocking in of my artwork.

<p>The saying 'Practice makes perfect' is definitely true in art insofar as the great art masters have often stressed on 3 underlying words, <strong>"PRACTICE, PRACTICE,PRACTICE!!!"</strong>
</p>

            

</body>

</html>



 
          
    